Guide to the Ed Wood, Jr. collection, 1966-2006.
Wood, Ed Jr. collection
- Series IV. Films
  - "The Incredibly Strange Film Show, volume 3: Ed Wood", Date unknown; DVD-2348
Location: Human Sexuality PN1995.9.S45 S89 1973 bk.2
Pages: 191 Published: 1973
[sequel to Censorship, Sex, & The Movies: Book 1]